A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Personnel Services, Office Files of Gerry Radovich FA502
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Administration, Personnel Services, Office Files of Gerry Radovich
1972-1983
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA502
3.8 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Pre-1972 Affirmative Action Files, 1964-1971 (Box 1)
- 1972 Affirmative Action Files -- General -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Reports, Meeting Materials, Grant Proposals and Recommendations, etc. (Box 1)
- 1973 Affirmative Action Files -- General -- Memoranda, Reports, Meeting Materials, Staff Profile, Background, etc. (Box 1)
- 1973 Affirmative Action Files -- Report, "The Ford Foundation as an Affirmative Action Employer", Mar 1973 (Box 1)
- 1973 Affirmative Action Files -- Report, "The Ford Foundation's Program in the Changing Role of Women", Mar 1973 (Box 1)
- 1973 Affirmative Action Files -- Robert A. Mayer Report Re: Affirmative Action and the Role of Women at the Ford Foundation (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Paper and Related Documents (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- General -- Correspondence, Memoranda (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Grade 1 and 2 Gains and Losses (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- March 1974 Statistics Re: Women and Minorities at Ford Foundation (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Memorandum and Statistical Appendices for Affirmative Action Committee, 5/1/1972-1/15/1974 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Men at Ford Foundation (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Minorities at Ford Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- November 18 Meeting on Affirmative Action in Higher Education (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Positions Filled at Ford Foundation Between 1972 and 1973 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Posted Positions at Ford Foundation Between 1972 and 1974 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Administration (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Asia and the Pacific (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Chairman, Office of the (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Education and Research, Office of the Vice President (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Europe and International Affairs (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Finance, Office of the Vice President (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Humanities and the Arts (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- International Division (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- International Division, Office of the Vice President (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Latin America and the Caribbean (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Middle East and Africa (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- National Affairs, Office of the Vice President (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Population (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- President, Office of the (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Public Broadcasting (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Reports (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Resources and the Environment (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff, Gains and Losses -- Secretary and General Counsel (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Professional Staff Statistics at Ford Foundation (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Promotions at Ford Foundation Between 1972 and 1974 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Puerto Rican Community Complaints Against Ford Foundation (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Reclassifications of Ford Foundation Positions, 1973 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Report, "Affirmative Action Program for the Employment of Women and Minorities on the Professional Staff of the Ford Foundation", Feb 1974 (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- September 1974 Statistics Re: Women and Minorities at Ford Foundation (Box 1)
- 1974 Affirmative Action Files -- Women at Ford Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Committee -- General -- Memoranda, Grant Recommendation (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Response to Mr. Bundy's Memo of May 28 (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Statistics (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Agenda, Meeting Materials (salary data) for 7/8/75 Affirmative Action Committee Meeting (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- "Background Material - Affirmative Action" Prepared for Meeting of Affirmative Action Advisory Committee (7/8/75) (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Ford Foundation Professional and Support Staff Statistics (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Minority Reports, Statistics (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Part-Time and Consultant Selection (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Position History Report (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Salary Data Report Prepared for the Affirmative Action Advisory Committee (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Salary Material of 7/75 Affirmative Action Report (not included in report) (Box 2)
- 1975 Affirmative Action Files -- Women's Reports, Statistics (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Committee Memoranda Re: Staff Appointments (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Reports (3/76) (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Report, Data (6/1/76) (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Report, Data for 9/76 Trustees Meeting (9/76) (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- "Recruiting and Affirmative Action Report - Professional Staff - Fiscal Year 1976" (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- Salary Comparisons, Men vs. Women (11/76) (Box 2)
- 1976 Affirmative Action Files -- Staff Profile Report for Mr. Bundy (3/76 and 9/76) (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Committee Meeting (2/1/77) (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Program Backups of Data, Statistics (1973-1978) (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Report (2/77) -- Backup to Statistics to 2/77 Report (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Report (2/77) -- Salary Material (not included in report), 1976 (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Report, Data (2/77) -- Supplement (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- "Background Material - Affirmative Action" Prepared for the Meeting of the Affirmative Action Committee (2/1/77) (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Minority Salary Comparison (March 1977) (Box 2)
- 1977 Affirmative Action Files -- Report of Degrees Granted to Women and Minorities, Feb 1977 (Box 2)
- 1978 Affirmative Action Files -- Affirmative Action Correspondence (Box 2)
- 1978 Affirmative Action Files -- Backup to 3/78 Affirmative Action Report (Box 2)
- 1978 Affirmative Action Files -- Report on Affirmative Action, Mar 1978 (Box 2)
- 1979 Affirmative Action Files -- Backup to 3/79 Affirmative Action Report (Box 2)
- 1979 Affirmative Action Files -- Bundy, McGeorge Letters (Box 2)
- 1979 Affirmative Action Files -- Report on Affirmative Action, Mar 1979 (Box 2)
- 1980 Affirmative Action Files -- Backup to 3/80 Affirmative Action Report, 1972-1980 (Box 2)
- 1980 Affirmative Action Files -- Report on Affirmative Action Originals and Backup Material, 1972-1980 (Box 2)
- 1980 Affirmative Action Files -- Report on Affirmative Action, Mar 1980 (Box 2)
- 1981 Affirmative Action Files -- Backup to 3/81 Affirmative Action Report (Box 2)
- 1981 Affirmative Action Files -- Correspondence on Affirmative Action Report (Box 2)
- 1981 Affirmative Action Files -- Report on Affirmative Action, Mar 1981 (Box 2)
- 1981 Affirmative Action Files -- Typed Charts (not used) (Box 2)
- 1982-1983 Affirmative Action Files -- 1982 Affirmative Action Report
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Budget Papers -- Memoranda and Budget Summaries, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Budgeted Positions for 1977, [1976] (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Changes in Fiscal Year 1977 Staffing (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Foundation Staff -- Salary Grades and Position Changes, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Management Costs (FY 1977) (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Schedule A's Re: Management Staff Projections, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Schedule A Forms (blank), [1976] (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 Budget Files -- Schedule A Instructions Re: Management Staff, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Memoranda Forwarding Salary Sheets, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Salary Memoranda to Trustees, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Performance Appraisals Covering Memorandum and Instructions, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Personnel Services, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Promotions -- Over/Under Guidelines, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Report, "The Ford Foundation Salary Survey", 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Salary Policy, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Salary Pool Figures Re: Foundation Programs and Departments, 1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1977 William P. Gormbley Files -- Salary Survey and Staff Compensation Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- Budget and Schedule A, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- Budgeted Positions, [1977] (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- General -- Memoranda, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- Management Costs -- Budget vs. Actual, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- Schedule A's Re: Management Staff Projections, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- Schedule A Statistics Re: Foundation Staff, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Budget Files -- Staffing, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Annual Performance Appraisal Memo and Instructions, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Backup of Salaries, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- General Re: Salary Increases, Gender Differences, Policy Revision, etc., 1976-1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Performance Appraisals, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Personnel Services Salaries, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Promotions/Special Cases, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Salary Form Letters, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Salary Literature/Data incl. Ford Foundation Salary Survey, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Salary Pools, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Schedule A Form and Instructions Re: Management Staff, 1977 (Box 3)
- Fiscal Year 1978 Salary Policy Files -- Trustees Memo Re: 9/77 Meeting on Salary Policy, 1977 (Box 3)